purchase.com 2011-12-05

# Privacy Policy for Purchase.com

Purchase.com's Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using Purchase.com.

By using or accessing Purchase.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

#### The Information Purchase.com Collects

When you register with Purchase.com, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, your gender, schools attended and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.

When you enter Purchase.com, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all Purchase.com visitors.

In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser.

You post Content (as defined in the Purchase.com Terms and Conditions) on the Site at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Purchase.com is a violation of the Purchase.com Terms of Service and should be reported through Guest Services.

Purchase.com may ask you to tell a friend about our site in which case we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will contact your friend in your name inviting him or her to visit Purchase.com, and may send reminders to them.

Purchase.com will store such tell-a-friend information. Your friend may contact us through the Help Center to request that we remove this information from our database.

Purchase.com may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other users of Purchase.com through the operation of the service (e.g., photo tags) in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience.

By using Purchase.com, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.

#### Children Under Age 13

Purchase.com does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for Purchase.com or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address.

No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on Purchase.com. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us through the form on our privacy help page.

#### Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18

We recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

#### Use of Information Obtained by Purchase.com

We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by Purchase.com that we think you may find valuable.

Profile information is used by Purchase.com primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to others permitted to view that information by your privacy settings

Purchase.com may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service.

Generally, you may opt out of such emails, though Purchase.com reserves the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.  

Purchase.com may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people on Purchase.com are interested in different products or services and personalizing advertisements and promotions so that we can provide you Purchase.com. We believe this benefits you.

#### Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, 2) legally required or, 3) permitted by you. To learn more about the operation of the service, we encourage you to read the tutorial here. To opt out of the service altogether, click here.

Like many other Web sites that interact with third party sites, we may receive some information even if you are logged out from Purchase.com, or that pertains to non-Purchase.com users, from those sites in conjunction with the technical operation of the system. In cases where Purchase.com receives information on users that are not logged in, or on non-Purchase.com users, we do not attempt to associate it with individual Purchase.com accounts and will discard it.

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the Purchase.com business, or individual business units owned by Purchase.com, Inc., were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

When you use Purchase.com, certain information you post or share with third parties, such as personal information, comments, messages, photos, videos, listings or other information, may be shared with other users. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk.

Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information anywhere (such as when posting comments, messages, photos, videos, listings or other items) this information may become publicly available.

#### Links

Purchase.com may contain links to other Web sites. Purchase.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Purchase.com.

#### Third Party Advertising

Advertisements that appear on Purchase.com are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content.

Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content.

In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. 

Purchase.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on Purchase.com unless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Purchase.com and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

#### Changing or Removing Information

Where you make use of the communication features of Purchase.com to share information with other individuals on Purchase.com you generally cannot remove such communications.

#### Security

Purchase.com takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of Purchase.com Web Site, please contact us through Guest Services.

#### Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of Purchase.com, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms and Conditions and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law.

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page.

We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact our Guest Services.

Thank you for reading the Purchase.com Privacy Policy. Purchase.com © 2011
